Any questions?
>> You can just um maybe give a update on
sort of where the stadium I know there's
a lot of different processes going on,
but specifically um the community
benefits agreement process sort of
getting underway and just generally
where you are in the stadium process.
>> Yeah, it um I mean everything a lot
first of all a lot of work. Um it's uh
uh you know Carrie, Demani, Tim, a lot
of folks from our team are are spending
a lot of time meeting with community
leaders uh city council members and um
you know it's an ambitious timeline that
we have and uh we won't be able to
accomplish our goals in terms of timing
and getting in there just by ourselves.
So it's not just something the Broncos
are driving. we've got to have a lot of
support from uh partners and and others
that are involved with the site.
>> How has that support been so far and and
sort of do you think you're on track
where you need to be in order to you
know make an ambitious time?
>> Yeah, no, the support has been good. Um
and everybody I think wants to do the
right thing, but again um there's
there's a lot of different parties with
with different interests. uh as of now
we're we're on track, but again it's
ambitious to get to the the 2031 uh goal
that we have.
>> When uh when do you anticipate you guys
will kind of shed the the preferred site
label and move towards that? Where are
you in that process?
>> Uh we're we're getting closer. Um, and
again, some important steps have been
taken, but um, uh, when we change that
from preferred site to this is the site,
we'll have all of our ducks lined up and
and be prepared to say we're we're
formally moving forward with that site.
Uh, not sure exactly when that's going
to be, but um, uh, hopefully sometime,
you know, in the coming months.
>> Obviously getting close to the new
facility being done. What's it been like
to see that go up? And then what sort of
benefit do you see in having everybody
in one location there?
>> Yeah, it's been uh a terrific process.
It's fun to watch that getting built
right before our eyes and and um uh Amy
D, who's been managing that that process
for us, has done a terrific job. So, uh
we're we're on time and on budget and um
uh we'll be moving in there uh in June.
And uh really the biggest advantage I'd
say two things. one is bringing the
whole organization together. So folks
from different buildings and and sites
including the stadium. Uh and then it's
going to be a huge benefit for the for
the players. So the whole uh design of
the building is oriented around enabling
the players to have that one floor where
they can do everything. So a larger
locker room, training room connected to
the wait room, meeting rooms, cafeteria,
um you know, the player path of travel
is going to be uh uh really well set up.
Greg, I know you said in January you had
zero concern about Bon Knicks's surgery
and it was straightforward. How have
things progressed with him that you've
heard, you know, in the last couple
months?
>> Uh, really really good. He um he's
attacked his uh recovery in the same way
that that he attacks, you know,
preparing for games and and just done a
a terrific job. He's ahead of schedule.
Uh no concerns at all for OTAAS and and
go forward from there. um really really
pleased with his progress and and you
know the support from Bo Lowry and
everyone. A
>> couple months ago you mentioned
opportunistically aggressive. That's how
you describe things. Would you certainly
say Jaylen Wadd that trade that's
exactly what you were talking about in
terms of that philosophy coming?
>> Yeah, that's that's exactly right. Uh
you know, we went into this and we were
prepared to be aggressive if we thought
there was an opportunity. Um at the same
time, we weren't going to be aggressive
just to be aggressive. So, we love the
guys that we have in our locker room on
our team. They're um they've been a um
you know, it's a strong core and really
good fit. And so, the bar was high. If
we were going to go get someone in free
agency uh that we thought could be um a
better addition. And the opportunistic
part was when we saw something to take a
big swing, we were we were going to be
willing to take a big swing. And and
that's what we did with uh with the
Waddle trade. And uh all of our
interactions with him so far have been
terrific. He's we think he's got all the
aspects that are important to us.
Obviously a tremendous playmaker uh but
also a great locker room guy. You know
he's got grit, professionalism, high
high level of intelle uh you know
intellectualness around football and and
um and his performance
>> when you guys run it back Greg with so
many of your own free agents. I think
that might be the first time that your
stewardship has been criticized like
you're not doing enough. Is waddle
enough as you sit here for a team that
was one game away from getting to the
Super Bowl.
>> I don't I don't know that we're ever
going to say we've taken all the steps
that are enough. So, we're always
looking what what more can we do. Um
we've got a you know, we're looking at
we start we're starting over and and
we've got a lot of hard work uh to do.
We still have the draft coming up. We've
got um training camp. Uh you know, we're
always going to be looking at
opportunities to make this team better
and I don't think we'll ever say we've
we've done enough.
>> Greg, keep young assistants. um in the
building when they're when they're
highly coveted. So to to be able to do
that with Davis and have him stepping
into a larger opportunity to call plays.
What what how how just critical did you
feel like that was kind of part of your
overall offse?
>> Yeah, I mean we're you know as you get
more successful, you're going to become
uh a place and a an organization that
other teams want to come uh hire your
your folks. Um and uh so we put a
priority on on retaining a number of
those and Davis Webb was one of them.
Um, we're excited to have him in that
role and and have a lot of confidence in
in him.
>> Yeah. What what did you think of Shawn
giving up play calling duties to Davis
and what that means about Davis?
>> Uh, you know, I think Shawn always wants
to do what's in the best interest of of
this team and the and the Broncos
organization. Uh, you know, this was we
he and I obviously talked about it, but
this was entirely 100% his decision. And
um uh I think it's going to be again
we've got a lot of confidence in Davis
and and I think uh Sean's going to be
very supportive of him.
>> Greg, back on the on the stadium note,
when you talk about this ambitious
timeline and you know obviously the the
parties involved, there's the concrete
yard, there's Denver water, like when
you say you need help specifically, what
what are you just kind of referring to
in that regard?
>> Yeah, again it's um it's help from and
input from the community. It's from city
council and the mayor. Um, and then, you
know, Denver Water is going to be an
important part uh of the process.
Obviously, it's a it's a utility that
provides a tremendous asset uh to the
community and and we need to make sure
that uh as we move forward that their
service isn't interrupted in any way and
and we're cognizant of that, but um but
also coming up with a with a plan that
allows us to get in there on the
timeline that we have in mind.
>> Greg, I have kind of two for you related
to the summit. one, what you think of
what we saw Saturday and then I asked
Rob Cohen this Friday about their new
stadium goals and how much have they,
you know, shared with you and vice versa
with dealing with the municipalities and
everything involved and how's that going
as they're obviously going to be your
neighbors every day too uh with, you
know, the site down south.
>> Yeah, we we haven't had a a lot of
communication with them on that. I know
our folks from our our teams, Demani
Leech and his his uh uh his team and
some others from uh from Summit have
talked. Uh I mean just to see the
excitement I think was uh was really
special and shows uh you know the
community and their their interest in
women's sports. I can say it was a
little strange to see all the green uh
in our stadium, but um uh but it I think
it was really good just to see the
support.
>> Time for a few more for Greg. Sean Sean
said at the combine he came out as
pushing for um George to get an
extension. How does that potentially
stand at this point?
>> Yeah, and I've said the same thing. We
we want to have uh George here long term
and and um he's been a a a terrific
partner for for Shawn and how they work
together and and I'm sure we'll we'll
get that sorted out.
>> Are there are there provisions in place
in case you have to go beyond 2031 with
the new stadium? Uh, I mean the the the
fallback would be to um and there's not
there's nothing in place right now, but
the fallback would would be to extend
our uh agreement with the current uh
stadium.
>> Right. At the at the community meeting a
couple weeks ago, I think the the
footprint is up to around 150 acres. Um
how much uh is that about where you
think it will end up? And then also as
it pertains to that concrete yard at the
top, how important is that that parcel
to what you're trying to accomplish with
the overall footprint? Yeah, I think
that that, you know, roughly 150 acres
is is about what the site will be. That
gives us obviously plenty of of land to
build a stadium and and do a development
around it. Um there's a number of of uh
private transactions that we're still
working on. Um the concrete company
being one of those and and um we're
going to try and get that done.
>> Have you guys landed
>> last one, Luca? And then Troy,
>> have you guys landed on a determination
between whether you you would like kind
of this to be privately owned, privately
owned stadium on private land or whether
you want to lease the land back to the
the city to build the stadium on top of?
>> Yeah, we're going to um without getting
into all the all the specifics, you
know, we've we've bought the land uh
privately. Uh we'll do that with the
other parcels. Um and we're going to
we're going to pay for the stadium to be
built. uh you know there'll be some
infrastructure support around it from
the city and and the state.
>> When I talked to him a couple years ago,
you told me you're tired of walking into
the meeting and seeing the chiefs, you
know, celebrating at these meetings. You
you knocked them out in terms of the
division. When you got as close as you
guys did, what did you learn from that
and kind of what's left to get to that
next goal?
>> Yeah. Um yeah, it's been nice to see a
little more attention on on the Broncos
uh in the in the video they play. We
talked about that that last night. Um
and uh but we we have a tremendous
amount of respect for for the uh teams
that are in our division. Uh everybody's
trying to get better. Um and that that's
the biggest takeaway is uh again we're
never going to feel satisfied. We don't
we're not going to feel like we've done
enough. So we're always going to be
pushing for uh that next level and and
what it takes to get there.